Lucy G. Barber 147 147
Stage
Lucy G. Barber Collection
1878-2011
Stage
147
36.25 linear feet; 27 boxes
The Lucy G. Barber Collection contains the research Barber conducted for the publication of Marching on Washington: The Forging of an American Political Tradition. In her book, Barber showcases how protesting in D.C. against wars or injustice become an American political norm. Research topics include Jacob Coxey's army, the Civil Rights Movement, Million Man March, Veterans Against the Vietnam War, and Woman Suffrage, among others.
Custodial History
Gift of Lucy Barber, 2013.
Biographical / Historical
The Lucy G. Barber Collection contains the research Barber conducted for the publication of Marching on Washington: The Forging of an American Political Tradition. In her book, Barber showcases how protesting in D.C. against wars or injustice become an American political norm. Barber shows how such highly visible events contributed to the development of a broader and more inclusive view of citizenship and transformed the capital from the exclusive domain of politicians and officials into a national stage for Americans to participate directly in national politics. Included in her research, are her findings regarding the March on Washington for Jobs and Justice on August 28, 1963. Barber was a 1984 Truman Scholar and received her B.A. in History from Haverford College in 1986 and her Ph.D. in History from Brown University in 1996. In 1995, she joined the faculty as an assistant professor in the history department at the University of California, Davis. In 2001, Barber left UC Davis for a position as an archivist at the California State Archives, where she worked on the online catalog project and began its electronic records efforts. In 2006 she was named Director for Technology Initiatives at the NHPRC, overseeing policy and grants for archival projects, especially those involving digitizing of historical materials, preservation of electronic records, and development of new tools and training programs.
Scope and Contents
The Lucy G. Barber Collection is comprised of research files for Barber's book, Marching on Washington: The Forging of an American Political Tradition. Research topics include Jacob Coxey's army, the Civil Rights Movement, Million Man March, Veterans Against the Vietnam War, and Woman Suffrage, among others.
- Series 1
  - 1973 People's Coalition for Peace and Justice Roving Demo, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mayday Evaluations, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - White House - 1971 June - August (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - White House Cost of Demos, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Congress 1971 Post Demo Investigation May (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - White House - 1971 September- December (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mayday Arrest Accounts, 1971-1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1971 Capitol Protest, 1972-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Post 1971 Policy, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - White House - 1972 Election Demo (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1973 January Protest, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - White House - 1973 Demos (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1971 Memories (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Responding to Local Protests, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1983 Capitol Bombing (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1979 National March - Gay and Lesbian, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Disabled Protests, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Recent Protests, 1985-1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Comment on Marches, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1971 Coverage - Overview (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - June - Magazine Report, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Radical Magazine Reports, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Medical Committee Reviews, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Legal Tests - Capitol Steps, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1971 June-August (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1971 September - December (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Coverage July - December, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - NY Times Overview Nov. 7, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Charles Tilly, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Park Police Interviews, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - April 25- May 2, 1878 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Social Movement Theory Unity, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Tichenor - President Social Movement, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Social Movement - Turnout, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Evans Article on German Crowds, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Thomas and Patterson Concus, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Washington - History Post, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Washington DC General, 1983-1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Washington - The White House, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Washington as Space - Article, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Washington as Public Space, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Precedents of Privileges Intro, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Roberts and Ward Protesting White House, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Washington - Right to Assemble, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Mixed up Book Notes, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1932 Veterans/Gold Star Mothers, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - DC Core - Post 1963, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - BK: 1st Amendment/Social Movement, 1993-2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - First Amendment/Free Speech, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Menelll "We - Images", 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Collective Action Readiness To Do, 1987-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Post Modern Political Theory, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - General Collective Action Work, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Social Movement Theory, 1983-1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chwe - Structure and Strategy, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Gartner and Segura - Invisibility, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Social Movement Theory: On Resisting Resistance, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Lipsky - Protest as a Political Resource, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Not US- WV China's Law, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Not US - Kowalenski, Militancy and USSR, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Not US Meade - Brazil - 1890-1917, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Not US - Lohmann, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Demos - Not US James - Daniel Peron, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - State Building/Nationalism, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Net and Organizing, 1990-2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Thompson - Moral Economy, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Munck - Social Movement Formation, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Media and Movements, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Political Culture, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Contemporary American, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Social Movement - US General, 1991-2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bill Moyer - Social Movement Empowerment Project, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Demonstration - History, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Holton - Crowd in History, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Lunn - Crowd, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Rituals/Procession, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Overview - Media and Movements, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Rock Concerts - Demonstrations, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Gender and Demos, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - DC History, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 1941 Chapter Comments, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 1941 Ad, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 1941 Ad, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Randolph Account of Cancellation, 1994-2011 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 1946 Act to Regulate Capitol (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - A Philip Randolph Oral History Transcript, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Adam Clayton Powell - Marching Blacks, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Reports on March in Washington, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 1941 "Don't Buy where you can't Work, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Greenberg Harlem, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Lash - Eleanor and Franklin, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Inaugural, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Scottsboro Parades, 1933-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1941 Library Work, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - March on Washington 7/42-12/42, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dalfiume - The "Forgotten Years", 1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Sitkoff, Militancy and World War II, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Kryder - Meetings and Management, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Crosswaith - Discrimination Incorporation, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - March on Washington Movement - 1943-1946 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - International Issues, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - FBI and March on Washington Movement, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Post March - Coverage of Blacks in Mainstream Press, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Coverage of March on Washington, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Granger Summary Article, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Victory Rally, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 1922 Anti- Lynching Parade, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 1920s Marches, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 1926 KKK March, 1925-1987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Post Bonus Army - 1934-1938 Permit Requests, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Wilma's Article, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Research Request Slips - Newspapers, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Plans and Views of Washington, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - To File, 1931-1933 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Graphs - March on Washington, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Hoover on Bonus, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Hoover Personality, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Parades 1920s - Law, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Demo in Europe 1930s, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Attitudes Towards Parades, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Klehn - Communist, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Size of Gov't, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Washington - As Space, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Veteran Predecessors, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Waters/Portland Connection, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Loan Payment Feb. 1931 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Political Power of Veterans, 1930-1932 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Veteran Benefits, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Other Parades, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Veterans December 31 - May 32, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1932 May 20 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1930s Police, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Military, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Veterans in Public, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - March. 6 1930 Unemployment Day, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cox's March, 1931-1932 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hunger March, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - BA Citizenship, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Who are the Marchers - Veterans Bureau, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Race and Bonus, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - June 1- Senate Hearing, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - June 8 - June 17, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Congressional Debate Jone, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - House Debate, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - June 7th Parade, 1932-1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Commissioners "Don't Send" Memo, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - June 1 - 6, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - June 18-30, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Hearing Group Representation, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Public Works - Programs, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Anti-Bonus Anti Lobbying, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Lobbyists in Washington, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Opinion of Politics - Pre 1932, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - B.E.F News, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - July 1-10, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - July 11-16, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Adjournment, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - July 16-July 28, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Communists, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Women - Survival, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Transportation - Veterans, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Army Education, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - BA Education Testimony, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Education Logs, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Education Newspaper Reports, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Evacuation: Orders, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Bonus March New, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1932 Groups New, 1926-1932 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Bonus March Memory, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Glassford Papers, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Bonus March Justice Department, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - ACLU and Bonus Marcher, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Lobbying, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Graves Article, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - FBI - 1920s Williams Article, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Assessment August, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Glassford Interview, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Post Bonus Army Marches, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Education - Johnstown Stage, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Aftermath - Bonus Agitation, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Aftermath - Fascist, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Decayed Reactions to Education, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Dec. 1932 Hunger March (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - BA Literature: Over White House, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - FDR's Inaugural, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Opinion of Hoover, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Post Bonus Army Marches, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Hoover et. Al Explanations Education, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Celebration DC 1940, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - DC and Demonstrations General, 1978-1991 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Allen Washington Police - 1886, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Notes for Chronology, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Media, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Denis Kerney, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Call to March 1877, 1906-1996 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - National Park Service, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Misc, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Popular Essays, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Slyvester's Police Book, 1894 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Precedent Civil War Parade, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Sources, 1988-1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Done, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - DC RG 351, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Sources Black Newspaper, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Photos of Coliseum DC Police, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Rogers - in search of, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Photo Research, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - National Archives Photo, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Doonesbury Cartoons, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Gay, Lesbian, Bi-Sexual and Transgender Rights (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Gay, Lesbian, Bi-Sexual and Transgender Rights (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Photos - March on Washington, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 1963 Figures (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Photos Coxey - 1894, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Figures Suffrage, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Suffrage Photo File, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - University of Texas, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Universal - Permission Request, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1971 May Day Tactical Manual, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Henry Vincent: The Story of Commonweal, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - New Stuff on Coxey, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1894 Road Policy, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - John Swinton - Call to March, 1886 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - New 1894 - Coxey Papers Guide Documents, 1955-1957 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - AHA Panel Proposal, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Coxey - Dame Novel, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Lobbyist Coxey, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Roads- Coxey, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Coxey: Petition/Broadside Jan 1894 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Coxey: On to Washingotn Bulletin 2 1/31/1894 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cap. Collier Story, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Coverage - After May 1, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Coxey's Army - Secondary, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Browne - Coxey, 1914-1944 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Misc. Review Coxey, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Coxey Secondary, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Coxey - Neutral, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Coxey - Positive, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Coxeyism: A Character Sketch, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Coxey Bibliography Work, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Public Works Program, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Unemployment (Coxey), undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Section VII - Who were the Protesters? Marginalization, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Section I Account of May 1st Parade, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Coverage - Pre Departure, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Political Implications Section VI, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Coxey - Governmental Response Section VI, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Section IV Press Related Materials, 1893-1894 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Coxeyism Section III - Initial Marginalization, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Coxeyism Newspaper Coverage, 1894-1993 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Coxey Bulletin Jan 1895 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Letter from Jail Coxey May 1894, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Veblen on Coxey, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Coxey - Western Armies, 1896 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - JP comments - 1963 March (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Part III Organization March, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Chapter Debate Part II, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Secondary Comments on Now, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 1963 Policing Secondary, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 1960s, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 1963 Attitude Toward Protest, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 1963 Washington DC, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Black Women Civil War Movement, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Black Justice - Eliff Article, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Sources 1963, 1988-1992 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Sandage Article - Lincoln Memorial, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Civil Rights Movement, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Political Culture - Steven Kelman, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Politics/Civil Rights Movement - Norrell, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Making the March on Washington For Jobs and Freedom, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - 1950s, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - 1958 Youth March, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Prayer Pilgrimage, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Chapter - Intro Notes Part I, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Part IV March, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Women and 1950s, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Government Celebrations in DC, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Peace/Anti War Marches Pre 1963, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - March on the Conventions, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1962 CR Inquiry DC and Pre 1963 Lort Activities, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Conclusion Materials, 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Marching in General - Conclusion, 1987-1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1963 Movies Sources, 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1913 Movies - Sources, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1983 March on Washington Commemoration, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 1963 Frank Kamney/Gay Contingent, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 1963 Lincoln Memorial/Memory, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Media and Blacks, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 1963 - ADP, 1987-1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Tom Khan, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - SNCC and 1963 March, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 1963 New- King - I Have a Dream, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Freedom Rides, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 1963 New Labor and March Pre March (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 1963 New Labor and March Post March, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Rustin - Post March, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - 1963 John Lewis Marches etc., undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Civil Rights Movement - Film - 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - 1963 Related, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - 1963 Working Notes (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - JFK and March - Cooption, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Civil Rights Movement and Lobbying, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Economic Goals - August, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Context - July, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Civil Rights - Goals, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Lobbying - Attitude to, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Historical Sense/Debate, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Organizing Manual #2, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Organizing Manual #7, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Women and March, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Finances of March, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Marshals, 1900 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Entertainment, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Media Before, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Puerto Rican Assassination Attempts, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Army, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Violence/CD/Alcohol, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Meeting w/ DC Feds Officials July, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Nazi's/Negative, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Race Relation in Washington, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - JFK Administration, 1965-1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Publicity August, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Black Press, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Congress Anti - March, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Response to Criticism Aug 9-16, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - 1960s Congress, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Congress Pro March, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Organizing August 1- 21, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Slogans, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - 1963 James Blues The March, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Congressional March, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Editing of Speech, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Pay of March, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - 1963 March Media, 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - International Coverage, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Memories - Afterward, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Aftermath and Leaders Bios, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Memories, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - 1960s Other Marches, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Commemorative - 1965, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Part V: Aftermath, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - After - Demos Plans, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Plans After March 1963, 1988-1995 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Post March Plans, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Aftermath Criticism, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Aftermath - Criticism, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Culture Protest - DC Core, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Core Protests, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Poor People's Campaign, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Tradition of the March, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 1983 March, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1993 March on Washington (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - JFK Library - 1963 March, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1963 March on Washington Sources, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 1963 Library Work, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Overview Articles, 1963-1993 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Rustin, 1964-1995 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Martin Luther King, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Randolph Blog, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Roy Wilkins - Autobiography, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - FBI Reports on March, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Religious and Labor Coalition, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Anna Hedgeman, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - CORE, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Student Non Violent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - LA Activities - CORE, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - DC Media Contracts, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - April - Planning, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Call to Action by Jame Farmer, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - May Organizing Notes - 1963, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Organizing July Notes, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Organizing June Notes, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Organizing August 21-28, 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - SCLC April 28 - May 5, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Women's March on the Pentagon, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - CS King - Letter, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - ACLU and NPAC March Pre April 24, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - NPAC April Planning 7, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - YVAW Publicity April, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Swathmore Peace Collection, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War Sources, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - George Wiley Papers - 1971-1963, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Sandra Ally - National Park Service, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - TV News Coverage - 1971, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Security and Other Arrangements, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Veterans Against the War Access Denial, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War Congress- Anti, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War Congress- Pro, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Planning DC Police 4/15, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Coverage, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War - 1971 April (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Veterans Against War - DC Government, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - 1971 April 24 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - NPAC April 20-23, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Communist Party and April 24, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - 1971 April 24 Not DC Protests (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - April 24 Reports, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 25)